<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ctf on Software and tech | Kristoffer Lorentsen</title>
    <link>https://krilor.github.io/categories/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ctf on Software and tech | Kristoffer Lorentsen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 07:11:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://krilor.github.io/categories/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A couple of tools from my first CTF event</title>
      <link>https://krilor.github.io/posts/tools-from-ctf-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 07:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krilor.github.io/posts/tools-from-ctf-event/</guid>
      <description>Attended my first CTF event yesterday, tghack for beginners. That introduced me to these nice tools:
 CyberChef - The Cyber Swiss Army Knife CTF crypto challenges pwntools - CTF framework and exploit development library for python  Just used CyberChef to disquise a message. Can you figure out which album title is behind these zeros and ones?
 01001011 01001100 01111011 01000001 01101110 01101111 01110100 01101000 01100101 01110010 00100000 01100010 01110010 01101001 01100011 01101011 00100000 01101001 01101110 00100000 01110100 01101000 01100101 00100000 01110111 01100001 01101100 01101100 01111101</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Ceasar cipher implemented in Vue.js</title>
      <link>https://krilor.github.io/posts/ceasar-cipher-in-vue-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 06:29:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krilor.github.io/posts/ceasar-cipher-in-vue-js/</guid>
      <description>Related to my recent interest in CTF, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a little time to implement a simple Ceasar cipher in Vue.js. It allows the user to replace letters with another letter some adjustable number of positions up or down the alphabet.
I did this partly because it&amp;rsquo;s a long time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done any Vue-related work and also because I find other online Ceasar cipher sites to be a bit clunky and not as user friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just did my first SQL injection!</title>
      <link>https://krilor.github.io/posts/i-just-did-my-first-sql-injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 08:19:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krilor.github.io/posts/i-just-did-my-first-sql-injection/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; and it felt good!
This week I spent a couple of hours finding my way through Norwegian Police Security Services new job application which required &amp;ldquo;hacking&amp;rdquo; to apply. See the solution on Reddit, GitHub and Kode24. I had a lot of fun trying to figure out the puzzles and it got me excited about learning more.
While I liked the challenge, I do tend to like to learn in a more structured way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>